Guide to the Edmund White Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 1991 Acquisition, Series I; 24.92; (27 boxes)
  - Financial Papers, 1964-1988
    - Contracts and payments, 1982-1983; 2 (Box 22)
    - Income tax return, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Maxine Groffsky Literary Agency, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
    - Bills and receipts, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Clippings, 1956-1991; (1 box)
    Series IV, Clippings, is divided into two sections, Interviews and Clippings about Edmund White. The material is arranged alphabetically by publication within each section.
    Interviews
    - Au Courant, 1982 December 20 (Box 22)
    - Bay Area Reporter, 1990 May 3 (Box 22)
    - The Blade, 1979 January 4 (Box 22)
    - Boston Globe, 1990 November 26 (Box 22)
    - Boston Phoenix, 1982 October 12 (Box 22)
    - Brown Daily Herald, 1989 April 14 (Box 22)
    - The Chicago Literary Review, 1980 June 6 (Box 22)
    - The Chicago Maroon, 1987 April 28 (Box 22)
    - Deutsches Allegemeines Sonntagsblatt, 1987 December 13 (Box 22)
    - Drummer, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Europeo, 1990 June 16 (Box 22)
    - The Fifth Freedom, 1981 April-May (Box 22)
    - Figaro, 1990 January 24-30 (Box 22)
    - The Gay, in Japanese, 1982 November (Box 22)
    - Gay Agenda, 1987 January (Box 22)
    - Gay Community News, 1979 April 21 (Box 22)
    - Gay Scotland, 1987 July-August (Box 22)
    - Gay Times, 1986 June (Box 22)
    - Gaysweek, 1979 January 15 (Box 22)
    - Impact, photocopy, 1980 February 6 (Box 22)
    - In Touch, 1983 May (Box 22)
    - Lambda, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Mandate, 1982 October (Box 22)
    - Masque, 1986 Spring (Box 22)
    - Le Monde, 1989 April 7 (Box 22)
    - NRC Handelsblad, in Dutch, 1986 December 10 (Box 22)
    - Nervure, 1989 March, October (Box 22)
    - New York Native, 1985 November 18-24 (Box 23)
    - Le Nouvel Observateur, 1984 June 8 (Box 23)
    - Out, 1986 March-April (Box 23)
    - Over to You, in English and Swedish, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Paris Review, 1988 Fall (Box 23)
    - The Pink Paper, 1988 January 28 (Box 23)
    - San Francisco Sentinel, 1990 April 26 (Box 23)
    - Stallion, 1983 January (Box 23)
    - Sydney Star Observer, 1988 April 1 (Box 23)
    - Time, 1990 July 30 (Box 23)
    - Time Out, 1988 January 20-27 (Box 23)
    - The Village Voice, 1988 June 26 (Box 23)
    - Clippings
      - Articles about Edmund White, 1982-1990, undated (Box 23)
      - Baltimore Gay Community Center: newspaper, 1979 January (Box 23)
      - Biography: Current Biography, 1991 January (Box 23)
      - Blue Boy, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
      - The Body Politic, 1979 June (Box 23)
      - Christopher Street, 1977 September (Box 23)
      - Christopher Street, 1978 March (Box 23)
      - Contre Ciel, 1984 May (Box 23)
      - Fag Rag, 1978 February-March (Box 23)
      - French language articles, 1982-1984, undated (Box 23)
      - Gay Community News, 1978 November 11 (Box 23)
      - Gay Community News, 1979 January 13 (Box 23)
      - Gay Communtiy News, 1979 June 23 (Box 23)
      - Gay Left, 1978-1979 Winter (Box 23)
      - Gayzette of the Baltimore Gay Alliance, 1979 Winter (Box 23)
      - Moja: Gay and Black, 1979 April 3 (Box 23)
      - NAMBLA News 1, 1979 Spring (Box 23)
      - Portland Scribe, 1978 June 22-28 (Box 23)
      - The Progressive, 1979 January (Box 23)
      - Seattle Times, 1978 November 9 (Box 23)
      - Tomorrow's Man, 1958 May (Box 23)
      - Toronto Xtra, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous, 1956-1990, undated; 4 (Box 23)
  - Personal Papers, 1940-1990; (1 box)
    Series V, Personal Papers, is arranged alphabetically by subject
    - Awards: Lambda Literary Award, Fund for Human Dignity Award of Merit, Gay News Book Award, William Whitehead Prize, 1980-1989; 4 (Box 23)
    - Astrological chart, undated (Box 23)
    - Baby book, 1940-1945 (Box 23)
    - Birth certificate: photocopy, 1940 January 13 (Box 23)
    - College transcript: University of Michigan, 1958-1962 (Box 23)
    - Cox, Christopher, funeral, 1990 September (Box 23)
    - Cranbrook School: Cum Laude Society, 1958 February (Box 23)
    - Diary: holograph, 1959, 1961 (Box 23)
    - Diplomas
      - Haven Intermediate School, 1954 June 18 (Box 23)
      - University of Michigan, 1962 June (Box 23)
    - French lessons: holograph, undated (Box 24)
    - High school papers: holograph and mimeograph, 1955, undated (Box 24)
    - Italian lessons: holograph, 1970 (Box 24)
    - Juvenilia, 1950-1955, undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - Juvenilia: artwork
    - Juvenilia: music, holograph
    - Memorabilia, undated (Box 24)
    - National Merit Scholarships Corporation certificate of merit, 1958 (Box 24)
    - Passports, 1966-1978 (Box 24)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 24)
    - Purcell, John: passport, 1975 (Box 24)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity: membership certificate, 1959 February 22 (Box 24)
    - Teaching materials, 1978 Fall (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund: portrait drawing, [1960?] (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund: yearbook entry, photocopy, undated (Box 24)
    - Yankee Recipe calendar, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Photographs, 1940-1989; (1 box)
    Series VI, Photographs, is arranged alphabetically by subject, with unidentified photographs found at the end of the series.
    - Brainerd, Joe and Edmund White, undated (Box 24)
    - Capote, Truman and Edmund White, photographed by Robert Mapplethorpe, undated (Box 24)
    - Corn, Alfred and Edmund White, undated (Box 24)
    - Cox, Christopher, 1978, undated (Box 24)
    - Cox, Christopher and Edmund White
    - [Fleming, Keith, and siblings?], undated (Box 24)
    - Gordon, Brad, [1980?] (Box 24)
    - Henderson, Gordon, undated (Box 24)
    - Howard, Richard, undated (Box 24)
    - McDermott, Keith, 1979 July, undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - [Merrill, James?], undated (Box 24)
    - Najmey, Ron, 1974 (Box 24)
    - Photograph album
    - Rose, Bill and Edmund White, undated (Box 24)
    - Schaefer, Marilyn, undated (Box 24)
    - Schaefer, Marilyn, with Edmund White and others, undated (Box 24)
    - Stack, Richard, undated (Box 24)
    - White, Delilah, undated; 3 (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund, 1970-1980, undated; 7 (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund: negatives, 1988-1989? (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund and Margaret, [1944?] (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund and Margaret: silhouette, [1940?] (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund, and others, 1967-1980, undated; 3 (Box 24)
    - White, Edmund V. [father], undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - White-Fleming family [2 photographs], undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - Williams, Tennessee, and Jim Gaines, undated (Box 24)
    - Unidentified, undated; 2 (Box 24)
  - Audiovisual Materials
    Conditions Governing Access
    Box 25 (audiocassettes and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes
      - Edmund White interview with Kay Bonetti, 1989; 1 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002109973587)
      - Edmund White reads Nocturnes for the King of Naples (chapter eight) and A Boy's Own Story (excerpt) / The Beautiful Room is Empty, undated; 1 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002109973595)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002109973603)
      - Kaleidoscope, Vaughan/Wilkinson, 1990 November 13; 1 (Box 25, Item barcode 3900210997361)
        Annotation reads: Aaron Copland's 90th birthday; Ciesinski Sisters; Trios; Conor Carson-Young Poet of the Year
    - Video Recordings
      - Margaret Fleming, undated; YCALMSS808_0031; 1; 00:07:16 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370690)
      - The Late Show, Edmund White, 1990 November 20; YCALMSS808_0032; 1 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370708)
      - CBS News Nightwatch; White, Holleran and Schulman, 1990 August 20; ycalmss808_0033; 1; 00:27:17 (Box 25, Item barcode 39002102370724)
  - Oversize
    - Writings
      - The Blue Boy in Black: scrapbook, 1962 (Box 26 (Oversize))
      - "Residence on Earth: Living with AIDS in the 1980s": Life, 1989 Fall (Box 26 (Oversize))
      - Maps: Santa Fe, Seattle, undated (Box 26 (Oversize))
      - Salt Lake City: Salt Lake Tribune, 1978 July (Box 26 (Oversize))
      - Texas: Upfront, 1979 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Articles about Edmund White, 1984 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Personal Papers
      - Juvenilia
        - Artwork, undated (Box 26 (Oversize))
        - Music, undated (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Photographs
      - Cox, Christopher, and Edmund White, undated (Box 27 (Oversize))
      - Photograph album, undated (Box 27 (Oversize))
      - White, Edmund, 1978-1980? (Box 27 (Oversize))
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 27 (Oversize))
- September 1991 Acquisition, 1969-1989; Series II; 0.21; (1 box)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, 1991.
  Contains correspondence and drafts of "A Woman's Place" and "To My Nephew." Correspondents include Margaret A. Fleming, Roy Fleming, and Dr. Johanna Tabin.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 190.
  Organized into two series: Correspondence and Writings.
  - Correspondence
    - Tabin, Joanna, typescript carbon, 1971 March 1 (Box 28)
    - Fleming, Roy, typescript letter signed, 1969 March 18 (Box 28)
    - Susan, includes "To My Nephew" typescript, poem, undated (Box 28)
    - Fleming, Margaret, 1969-1989 (Box 28)
  - Writings
    - "A Woman's Place", typescript, mimeograph, undated (Box 28)
- May 1993 Acquisition, 1950-1992; Series III; 4.5; (6 boxes)
  Gift of Edmund White, 1993.
  Contains correspondence, writings, including a biography of Jean Genet and The Last Days of New York, photographs, miscellaneous slides and tapes, and printed material.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 287.
  Organized into four series: Correspondence, Writings, Writings of Others, and Other Papers.
  - Correspondence
    - A-Z General, 1988-1992, undated; 25 (Box 29)
      Stephen Barber, David Bergman, Citizens Bank, M.C., Maxine Groffsky, New England Telephone, Robert Prager, Rogers, Coleridge, & White Ltd, Patricia Willis
    - First name only, 1989-1992, undated; 20 (Box 29)
      Correspondents inlcude: Al, Bob, Carolyn, Eccy, and Mother.
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1992, undated (Box 29)
    - Funeral Arrangements, 1992; 2 (Box 29)
  - Writings
    - Faber Book of Gay Short Fiction, 1992; 6 (Box 30)
    - Jean Genet Biography, 1950-1991, undated 1950-1991, undated; 7 (Box 30)
  - Writings of Others
    - Barber, Stephen: Obsession, undated; 2 (Box 30)
    - The Family of John Woodard, Sr., outline, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 30)
  - Other Papers
    - Personal, [circa 1990-1992]; 3 (Box 30)
    - Printed material: House and Garden, ISIS, Venice Magazine, Vanity Fair, Out, Straight Lines 7, circa 1990-1992; 2 (Box 30)
    - Postcards, undated; 2 (Box 31)
    - Genet Manuscript, undated; 15 (Box 31)
    - Notebooks and Journals, 1974, 1987, undated; 4 (Box 31)
      Received Ideas, The Last Days of New York, Orlando
    - Paintings, undated; 2 (Box 32)
    - Photographs, 1976-1979; 2 (Box 32)
    - Slides, undated (Box 32)
    - Honorary degree from Brown University, 1990 (Box 32)
    - Wallet, undated (Box 32)
    - Ephemera, undated; 3 (Box 32)
  - Oversize
    - Drawings, undated (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Audiovisual Materials
    Box 34 (audiocassettes and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "AIDS & the Responsibility of the Writer", Sarah Schulman, Essex Hemphill, Susan Griffin, Pat Califia, John Preston, San Francisco (audiocassette), 1990; 1 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002109973785)
    - "Duke II", undated; YCALMSS808_0021; 1; 00:14:58 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002102339687)
    - Unidentified, undated; YCALMSS808_0022; 1; The tape will not play. It appears to be blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 34, Item barcode 39002102339695)
    - "Waiting", undated; YCALMSS808_0023; 1; 00:11:04 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002102339703)
    - "A Day in the Life of Edmund White," rough cut no. 1, 30 minutes, no narration, undated; YCALMSS808_0024; 1; 00:31:17; A time code runs through the video. (Box 34, Item barcode 39002102339711)
    - "A Day in the Life of Edmund White," rough footage, image only, 2 hours approximately, undated; YCALMSS808_0025; 1; 01:44:35; A time code runs through the video. (Box 34, Item barcode 39002102339729)
    - "Allegro Serioso", Edmund White (audiocassette), 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002109973793)
      Annotation on the audiocassette reads: All my love - GIR
    - REM, Gene - Immunology (audiocassette), undated; 1 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002109973801)
    - John Weiners, NYC (audiocassette), early 1970s; 1 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002109973819)
    - Untitled (microcassette), undated; 1 (Box 34, Item barcode 39002109973827)
- August 1993 Acquisition, 1984; Series IV; 0.67; (2 boxes)
  Contains material relating to Genet: A Biography, including nine autograph manuscript notebooks for Chapter II and eight untitled notebooks.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 292.
  Not arranged in any particular order.
  - Biography of Jean Genet, notebooks, 1984, undated; 5 (Box 35)
  - Biography of Jean Genet, notebooks, undated; 4 (Box 36 (Oversize))
- August 1993 Acquisition, Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  Contains book reviews, interviews, and printed versions of Genet: A Biography.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 308.
  - Newspapers, 1993; 3 (Box 37 (Oversize))
- June 1994 Acquisition, 1981-1992; Series VI
  Contains letters from Edmund White to Margaret Fleming and Delilah White.
  Former call number: Uncat Za Ms 416.
  Purchased from Margaret A. Fleming on the Donald Windham-Sandy Campbell Collection Endowment Fund, 1994.
  - Letters from Edmund White to Margaret Fleming and Delilah White, 1981, 1992, undated (Box 38)
- September 1994 Acquisition, undated; Series VII; 0.21; (1 box)
  Gift of Edmund White, 1994.
  Contains audiocassettes dictated by Edmund White for Pyrography and Watermarked.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 405.
  Box 38 (audiocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Pyrography, begin, Part II (1 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973645)
  - Pyrography, conclusion, Part III (2 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973652)
  - Watermarked, sides 1 and 2 (1 of 3 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973660)
  - Watermarked, parts 3 and 4 (2 of 3 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973678)
  - Watermarked, part 5 (3 of 3 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973686)
- December 1994 Acquisition, Series VIII; 1; (1 box)
  Contains publishers' copies of Genet: A Biography and The Burning Library.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 416.
  - The Burning Library, proofs, 1994; 18 (Box 39)
  - Genet: A Biography, proofs, 1994; 17 (Box 39)
- April 1995 Acquisition, 1969-1990; Series IX; 2; (2 boxes)
  Gift of Edmund White, 1995.
  Box 41 (videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Contains correspondence, notes, photographs, printed material, writings and audiovisual material by and about Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 590.
  - Miscellaneous typescripts and printed materials, 1969-1990, undated; 38 (Box 40)
  - Three Friends, typescript, undated; 2 (Box 40)
  - "The Day the Shit Happened" Copy 1, 1993 April 16; ycalmss808_0003; 1; 00:31:19; A time code runs through the video. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339497)
    A handwritten letter, dated 1993-04-19, is included with the tape. It reads: Dear Ed - Well - here it is. I feel weird about it at this point, too close, my eyes are fried. Worked really hard on it this weekend. Didn't sleep Friday night - then Saturday when the edit was at last over went out w/ this new boyfriend: Abraham, 23, from Senegal (on parle francais, quoi!) so totally handsome! We are taking it slow - he told me his dick was "wild"! Dancing til 3, really romantic and nice. I am so fried though and really look like shit. So that all can wait. I hope he can come to the screening this Saturday. Man, I wish you guys could be there - it'd be great! Oh - I sent two because I thought before you left you could drop one to John [Seagliati] with a note, maybe that would work. Also - credits still need to be added - that will be fun to see. And - SECAM French version I'll send to Paris for Herbert to see ASAP. Sub-titling in English will be done this week in advance of the screening. Talk to you soon. Love, B P.S. I think the idea of having me speak to the camera during the credits about how I feel is a really good idea.
  - "The Day the Shit Happened" Copy 2, 1993 April 16; YCALMSS808_0004; 1; 00:34:55 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339505)
  - "I, Istanbul" and "Turquoise Coast", undated; YCALMSS808_0005; 1; 01:53:43 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339513)
    The video begins with a half-hour episode of Dream On.
  - "And the Band Played On", undated; YCALMSS808_0006; 1; 04:06:49 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339521)
    The original cover of this tape was originally labeled "A Day in the Life of Ed White". The tape is of the film "And the Band Played On".
  - Soap operas, Bill Clinton news conference, and AIDS segment, undated; YCALMSS808_0007; 1; 02:45:51 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339539)
    This tape's contents include soap operas, a Bill Clinton news conference, and AIDS content. It originally was labeled Larry Kramer PBS.
  - Bob Hope movie, soap operas, undated; YCALMSS808_0008; 1; 01:00:20 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339547)
    This was originally titled Stimpy Turkey. It shows a black and white movie with Bob Hope. The tape ends with a soap opera.
  - "Turkey: Ageless Beauty Modern Charm", undated; YCALMSS808_0009; 1; 00:40:48 (Box 41, Item barcode 39002102339554)
    At 00:16:32, one of the "Lethal Weapon" movies is partially recorded.
    A telegram for Edmund White is included with the tape. It reads: "Arriving Malaga Sunday Flight 363 1120 PM Lelter coming [am] ecstatic love Brookie". Also annotated, "enjoy being a girl".
- May 1995 Acquisition, undated; Series X; 1; (1 box)
  Contains two photocopies of the typescript for Genet: A Biography, with comments and proofs.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 439.
  - Jean Genet: A Biography, two photocopies, undated; 22 (Box 42)
- June 1995 Acquisition, undated; Series XI
  Contains audiocassette with dictation of "Cinnamon Skin."
  Former call number: Uncat ZA File 336.
  - "Cinnamon Skin", (1) just this side (1 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973629)
  - "Cinnamon Skin" (2 of 2 microcassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002109973637)
- November 1995 Acquisition, 1980; Series XII; 0.21; (1 box)
  Gift of Patrick Merla, 1995.
  Contains After Dark, Vol.13, no. 5, which includes "Sweating Mirrors," by Edmund White and Christopher Street, Vol. 4, no. 7, which includes "First Love," by Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 465.
  - After Dark, volume 13 number 5, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Christopher Street, volume 4 number 7, 1980 March (Box 43)
- December 1996 Acquisition, 1973-1982; Series XIII
  Gift of Marilyn Schaefer, 1996.
  Contains clippings, concerning works by Edmund White, including A Boy's Own Story.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA File 372.
  - Clippings, 1973-1982 (Box 43)
- January 1997 Acquisition, 1982-1996; Series XIV; 10.21; (11 boxes)
  Purchased from Edmund White on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 1997.
  Contains correspondence, writings, notebooks, printed material, including clippings, audiotapes, videotapes, photographs, and other ephemera by, or relating to Edmund White.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 520.
  Box 53 (audiocassettes and videocassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Boxes 54 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 44)
  - "Letters Aug. 1993-", 4 (Box 44)
  - "Letters 1993-4", 1993-1994; 6 (Box 44)
  - "Unmarked box with video of Genet", undated (Box 44)
  - "Articles about Genet, me", 1983-1994; 5 (Box 44)
  - "Correspondence 1988", 1987-1988; 9 (Box 44)
  - "1995 Articles about me", 1995-1996; 8 (Box 45)
  - "Stories by me", 1993; 4 (Box 45)
  - "Articles by me, 1995", 1993-1996; 8 (Box 45)
  - Manuscript and notes for Farewell Symphony, 1996; 12 (Box 45)
  - "Letters May 1993-" (Box 46)
  - "Letters May 1994", 9 (Box 46)
  - "Letters May 1995" (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence Oct. 1992", 1991-1993; 4 (Box 46)
  - Unidentified manuscript (essays- The Burning Library?), undated; 6 (Box 46)
  - Manuscript: The Burning Library, 1994 (Box 46)
  - "Letters May 1993-Aug 1993", 1992-1993; 7 (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence 1992 May-Oct", 1991-1992; 8 (Box 47)
  - "Letters May 1995", 9 (Box 47)
  - Materials removed from various groupings of correspondence and manuscripts, undated; 5 (Box 47)
  - "Articles about me 1994", 1993-1994; 9 (Box 47)
  - "Articles about me 1993", 6 (Box 47)
  - "Articles about me 1992", 1989-1996; 5 (Box 48)
  - "Letters Dec 1993-", 1992-1994; 5 (Box 48)
  - "Correspondence 1990-", 1992-1993; 3 (Box 48)
  - "Unlabelled" printed material, undated; 2 (Box 48)
  - Photographs removed from correspondence, 1987, 1995; 2 (Box 48)
  - "Correspondence 1985-May 1986", 1985-1986; 9 (Box 48)
  - "End of 1987 correspondence", 8 (Box 49)
  - "Letters Jan 1995", 1994-1995; 5 (Box 49)
  - "Envelope-'Letters from this bummer'?", 1984-1985; 4 (Box 49)
  - "Correspondence 1985-May 1986", 1985-1986; 7 (Box 49)
  - "Correspondence received 1986-May 1987", 1985-1986; 5 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, notebooks, writings, clippings, 1983-1992; 15 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, notebooks, writings, clippings, 1983-1992; 6 (Box 51)
  - Correspondence (box labelled: "Letters 1980's--Rorem, Coleman Dowell, Michael Lynch", 1982-1985; 6 (Box 51)
  - Farewell Symphony Mss, Boxes 1 and 2, undated; 5 (Box 51)
  - Farewell Symphony Mss, Boxes 1 and 2, undated; 10 (Box 52)
  - Notebooks, undated; 3 (Box 52)
  - Cineteve presente "La Passion Selon Jean Genet," 45 minutes, undated; ycalmss808_0026; 1; 00:46:19; SECAM (Box 53, Item barcode 39002102339737)
  - Cineteve presente dans la serie "Un Siecle d'Ecrivains" - France 3 "La Passion Selon Jean Genet," un film de Michel Van Zele, 45 minutes, undated; YCALMSS808_0027; 1; 00:45:59 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002102339745)
  - "The Late Show Neil Bartlett", 1993 November 17; YCALMSS808_0028; 1; 00:40:54 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002102339752)
  - "Apres le Deluge Secam", 1992 October 20; YCALMSS808_0029; 1; 00:14:58; SECAM (Box 53, Item barcode 39002102339760)
  - "The Late Show Neil Bartlett", 1993 November 17; YCALMSS808_0030; 1; 01:02:10 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002102339778)
  - "An interview with Delilah White" by Dorothy Austin, 1988; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973744)
  - Edmund White reads Nocturnes for the King of Naples (chapter eight) and A Boy's Own Story, (excerpt) / Edmund White reads The Beautiful Room is Empty (chapter two), undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973751)
  - Edmund White, FG Emission, [1993?]; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973777)
  - Interview with Philipp Kreiselmeyer for [?] before lecture, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109973769)
  - Computer media, (2 computer disks)
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    1997-ycal-0122-r-0001: untitled.
    - MAC format. System 7.5.1 Microsoft Word 5 May '96, 1997-ycal-0122-r-0001; 1 (Box 54)